photoshopstar.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy |

At PhotoshopStar.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by PhotoshopStar.com and how it is used. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, PhotoshopStar.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on PhotoshopStar.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Third party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to this website. No personally identifiable information is collected by these cookies. You can opt out of third party vendor’s cookies at any time by visiting this page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

PhotoshopStar.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. PhotoshopStar.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers respective websites. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.photoshopstar.com/contact/).
